Md Atikujjaman

mdatikujaman81@gmail.com 07359208450

3 Gearing Close London Greater London SW17 6DJ

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

I am a passionate frontend developer with a love for creating beautiful and interactive websites. I have a strong foundation in JavaScript, HTML, and CSS, allowing me to bring designs to life and provide engaging user experiences. Additionally, my knowledge of SQL enables me to work with databases effectively. also have experience with Python and basic familiarity with C# and C++.

WORK HISTORY

Healthcare Advisor

November 2021 - Present

Part time Boots 21-23 St john's road,London

• • In Charge of store and all till systems opening and closing . • I give advise to customer about medicine and other's boots product. Smoothly processed incoming online orders and booking store goods. • Virtually help customers and other advisors w

Waiter July 2021 - November 2021

Part time | Akash Tandoori | 70 Northcote rd, London

• In charge of all business activities, sales, and client relations • Served up to 85 guests each evening while smoothly processing incoming orders and managing over 200 Transactions every evening.

Customer Assistant

March 2021 - July 2021

Part time | The Food & Drink store | London

• • Guiding customers to the items they need. • Refilling the supermarket shelves as items run out and helping customers check out.

EDUCATION

BSc (Hons)

University of Roehampton - 2024

Computer Science

- Computer Systems - Computing and Society - Database - Mathematics for Computer Science - Software Development 1 - Software Development 2 - Algorithm - Operating System - Software Development 3 - Software Engineering - Data Science - Artificial

Intelligence - Operating Systems

International foundation year

Kingston University - 2021
Science, Engineering and Computing passed with 68% overall Applied mathematics - Pure mathematics - Computing

SKILLS

CSS, HTML, Javascript, Microsoft Excel, SQL, Python, C#

REFERENCES

References available on request